hoursmap.com 2019-05-13

# HoursMap: Explore your neighborhood.

## Privacy Policy

Welcome to HoursMap. Please read the following policy ("Policy") to understand how your personal information will be treated on Our website ("Our Site"). As used in the Policy "We", "Us", "Our" and "HoursMap" refer to Simon Yang, Inc., DBA HoursMap, and all the agents, contractors, subsidiaries, parents, affiliates, successors, and assigns of Simon Yang, Inc., if applicable. The Policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically.

**Type of Information**

Welcome to HoursMap. Please read the following policy ("Policy") to understand how your personal information will be treated on Our website ("Our Site"). As used in the Policy "We", "Us", "Our" and "HoursMap" refer to Simon Yang, Inc., DBA HoursMap, and all the agents, contractors, subsidiaries, parents, affiliates, successors, and assigns of Simon Yang, Inc., if applicable. The Policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically.

Every time you visit Our Site, you may be providing some of the following information:

  * anonymous statistics, and
  * personally identifiable information that you give Us.

We do not collect personal information about you unless you provide it to Us. This means that you can visit Our Site without telling Us who you are or revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself (such as your email address).

**How We Collect and Use Anonymous and Aggregate Data**

Anonymous and aggregate data do not reveal a visitor's identity. You do not have to register with Our Site before We can collect this anonymous information. We automatically receive and record information in Our server logs from your browser. We may collect anonymous information on your activity such as:

  * operating system;
  * Internet service provider;
  * IP address;
  * browser type;
  * pages viewed on Our Site, time each page was visited, and time spent on each page; and
  * referring URL.
  * personally identifiable information that you give Us.

We gather anonymous data so that We can produce aggregate reports for internal use and for use by other parties, including Our advertisers. Aggregate reports deal with aggregate behavior on Our Site, not individual behavior. For example, We can inform Our advertisers how many visitors saw or clicked on their ads and how many visitors saw or clicked on ads in different parts of Our Site. We do not include any personally identifiable information about you or your individual online usage patterns.

Our Site may use third party service providers to serve ads and emails on Our behalf. For this purpose, We may also provide these third party service providers anonymous data about visitors' site navigation.

We may place banner ads and links on third parties' websites. When We do this, We may also collect non-personally identifiable information through the aid of such third parties using cookies or other means. Collecting this anonymous data helps Us target Our Internet advertisements.

**Individual Visitor Information**

You can choose to provide individually identifiable information to Us in a number of ways through Our Site. For example, by ordering a service from Us, registering, sending Us email, registering to receive news or information, applying for a job, or entering sweepstakes or contests.

**Registration.** If you sign up with Our Site for a listing, We will collect personally identifiable data from you through the registration forms in order for you to register, maintain, and modify your listing.

If you sign up as a user, We also collect personally identifiable data from you.

If you sign up as an associate in our referral program, We also collect personally identifiable data from you.

When you request modifications to or deletions of your account information, in order to process your request, We also collect personally identifiable data from you . Should you ever need to, you can change or correct information about yourself and your account by signing in and editing your account information.

**Email to Friend.** If you elect to use Our "Email to Friend" feature, We ask you for your friend's email address and your email and name (optional). We will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit Our Site and will not store the information related to your friends. The one-time email sent pursuant to your use of the feature will be Our only contact with that person.

**Correspondence.** If you contact Us, We may keep a record of that correspondence and We may collect your email address and contact information.

**Surveys or Contests.** From time to time, We may conduct surveys, contests or sweepstakes on Our Site. If you participate in these surveys, contests, or sweepstakes, We collect personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use of Our Site. We may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys or contests.

**How We Treat Personally Identifiable Data.**

As a general rule, We do not release personally identifiable information to an unaffiliated third party without your permission unless We have a business relationship with those companies where the disclosure is appropriate.

For example, We may hire outside companies as contractors or agents to provide Us with services such as authorization and processing of credit card transactions, customer service, order or service fulfillment, contest or sweepstakes fulfillment, or We might be engaged in a joint venture or partnership with a company to offer special services to you. Furthermore, We may provide information to credit bureaus or provide information or sell receivables to collection agencies to obtain payment for Our offered products and services.

Upon occasion, We may decide to stop providing a service. In that event, We may provide personally identifiable information to a third party so that they can offer you the same or similar services. In these situations, We provide information to such third party only as needed to accomplish Our business objectives.

We may also send personally identifiable information to third parties if you have given Us your explicit permission to share this information. We may also provide personally-identifiable information if We believe, in good faith, that such action is necessary to

  * (i) respond to Your requests for customer service;
  * (ii) comply with law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request;
  * (iii) investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, or other action that otherwise violates Our Site's Terms of Use, any of Our guidelines, policies, or agreements;
  * (iv) respond to claims that you violate the rights of a third party;
  * (v) protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Us, Our subscribers, advertisers, users, or third parties; or
  * (vi) minimize costs and maximize accuracy with administrative agencies (e.g., We might share information with the Postal Service so that We may qualify for or continue to receive reduced postage rates).

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small data file that a website may send to your browser and which may then be stored on your system. It provides a way for a server to recall a previous request or previous registration or to keep track of a transaction.

We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. For the session cookie, once you close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your Internet browser's help file directions. You do not have to be registered with Us before We can use cookies.

Cookies tell Us nothing about you personally, unless you elect to give Us additional information about yourself.

Generally, We may use cookies to:

  * store your personalized features and preferences within Our Site, such as your bookmarks;
  * store your past activity on Our Site, such as recently visited locations and addresses;
  * require you to re-enter your password after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect access to your account;
  * process subscribers' listing service orders;
  * track your progress, number of entries, and status in some of Our sweepstakes and contests;
  * determine whether you are using a public computer so that any of Our settings that changed while you were using a public computer do not affect the next visitor's ability to use Our Site;
  * estimate the number of visitors and extent of repeat usage;
  * track visits to the Business Signup link; and
  * measure certain traffic and usage patterns, such as your IP address, operating system used, your internet service provider, the areas of Our Site you have visited, time each page was visited, the browser used, the website through which you came to Our Site, and your visiting patterns.

We link cookies to information you have provided Us.

**Disable Cookies**

You can always disable the cookie function if you choose. Our Site will still be viewable, even though you may lose the ability to use some of Our Site's advanced features.

**Web Beacon**

We may also use a web beacon, also referred to as a clear gif or pixel tag, which is a line of code that may be installed on some of Our web pages to collect anonymous usage data, such as which advertisements brought a visitor to Our Site, page views on Our Site, and which areas of the Site are more visited than others. These web beacons may also be used to deliver cookies.

**Mergers and Bankruptcy**

In the event We go through a merger, sale of company or assets, or bankruptcy, your personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

**Third Party Information Gathering**

Banner and display ads as well as listings may contain cookies and may perform other visitor activity tracking other than described herein. Information collected through such cookies is collected by a third party independently of Us. For more information about each third party provider, please refer to such third party's privacy policy.

**Links to Other Sites**

Our Site contains links to other websites on the Internet. Please be aware that We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave Our Site and to read the privacy statements of each website that collects personally identifiable information.

**Email Communication from Us**

We may use email to communicate with you, respond to your email, confirm orders placed online, and send information that you have requested.

We might also send you email to bring you important news such as functionality changes to Our Site or services or special offers you might find valuable. This email is only sent to you if you have chosen to opt in when registering. 

**Opt-out**

If you receive unwanted email from Us, you may remove yourself from Our email list by following the "unsubscribe" instructions in the email. Please note that if you do go through this process, you may continue to receive emails, although not those dealing with commercial solicitations. For example, We may email you about viruses, changes to your service, or other advisories.

**How We Handle Your Security**

When you place an order, We use a secure server to encrypt your information using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. The payment information is transmitted to the appropriate financial institution during processing.

**Special Notification with respect to Children's Privacy (Children under the age of 13)**

In response to concerns about protecting children's privacy online, Congress enacted the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 ("COPPA"), which sets forth rules and procedures governing the ways in which websites may collect, use and disclose any personal information for children under the age of 13. In accordance with Our Policy and COPPA regulations, We do not:

  * (i) request or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 years of age; or
  * (ii) knowingly use or share personal information from children under 13 years of age with third parties.

It is possible that by fraud or deception We may receive information pertaining to children under 13. If We are notified of this, once We verify the information, We will delete the information from Our servers.

Our Site may contain links to websites that collect such information. These companies are expected to comply with all laws pertaining to the collection of information from children. Because the Internet offers open access to a wide range of information, it is important that parents supervise and prevent access to inappropriate content, email or chat sessions.

Questions regarding children's privacy should be directed to:

HoursMap  
Attn: Privacy  
125 University Ave.  
Suite 205  
Palo Alto, CA 94301  
Email: privacy@mtrot.com  

**Scope and Changes to this Privacy Policy**

This Policy covers how We treat personal information that We collect and receive on Our Site, including information related to your past interactions with Our Site. This Policy supercedes and replaces all previously posted privacy policies. Any content You post to publicly accessible areas is not subject to Our Privacy Policy.

From time to time We may amend this Policy. Should We make substantial changes in the way We use your personal information, We will alert you by posting an announcement on Our Site or on another website about which You have been notified. We invite you to return as often as possible to check for any such announcement.

**Questions or Suggestions**

If you have any questions or suggestions, please contact Us at privacy@mtrot.com.
